{
    "id": "bf2c948fdba74c6f8fdbaa0eab8b98a0",
    "title": "Kinds Of Sentences",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Where have you been all this while?",
            "description": "An interrogative sentence asks a question.",
            "answers": [
                "Exclamatory",
                "Declarative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Imperative"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He took voluntary retirement last year.",
            "description": "A declarative sentence makes a statement.",
            "answers": [
                "Exclamatory",
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative",
                "Interrogative"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Bravo, you’re doing quite well!",
            "description": "An exclamatory sentence expresses a sudden emotion.",
            "answers": [
                "Exclamatory",
                "Imperative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Declarative"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Put it down.",
            "description": "An imperative sentence expresses a command, order or entreaty.",
            "answers": [
                "Imperative",
                "Exclamatory",
                "Declarative",
                "Interrogative"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She lives in a small town with her husband and children.",
            "description": "A declarative sentence makes a statement.",
            "answers": [
                "Exclamatory",
                "Declarative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Imperative"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t remember his name.",
            "description": "A declarative sentence makes a statement.",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Exclamatory"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She forgot to lock the door before going out.",
            "description": "A declarative sentence makes a statement.",
            "answers": [
                "Exclamatory",
                "Imperative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Declarative"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "What did you do with the money?",
            "description": "An interrogative sentence asks a question.",
            "answers": [
                "Interrogative",
                "Exclamatory",
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t want to leave now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Imperative",
                "Declarative",
                "Exclamatory",
                "Interrogative"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Give me a ring.",
            "description": "An imperative sentence expresses a command, order or entreaty.",
            "answers": [
                "Exclamatory",
                "Imperative",
                "Declarative",
                "Interrogative"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How disgusting!",
            "description": "An exclamatory sentence expresses a sudden emotion. ",
            "answers": [
                "Imperative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Exclamatory",
                "Declarative"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What a pleasant surprise!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Interrogative",
                "Exclamatory",
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}